<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T0XICITY</title>
    <link>https://T0XICITY.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on T0XICITY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Patrick Klingenberg</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:41:28 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://T0XICITY.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development process of this website</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:41:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/this-website/</guid>
      <description>How i got the idea to create a static website This website was created during my semester break. originally I had an unused Raspberry Pi 3 that i wanted to use as a webserver for hosting a website using the Wordpress Content-Management-System.
Long story in brief - I installed LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP) on the pi and found that the performance of the website was not exactly what I had in mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:21:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>The first post in my new blog. It is for testing some basic functions.
Text
 Quote:
&amp;quot;Success is not final; failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts.&amp;rdquo;
-Winston S. Churchill
 FAT
 First ordered list item Another item   Unordered list can use asterisks   Or pluses +  Some code: #include &amp;lt;iostream&amp;gt; using namespace std; int main() { cout &amp;lt;&amp;lt; &amp;#34;Hello, World!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our enterprise. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the Patrick Klingenberg. The use of the Internet pages of the Patrick Klingenberg is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from the data subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>## About</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this website is to provide me with a medium in which I can publish my thoughts and work on topics that interest me. On the one hand, this has the purpose of allowing me to recapitulate topics for myself and, in addition, to make them available to other interested parties.
The name T0XICITY is derived from the song Toxicity by the fantastic band System of a Down ♪♫</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>