<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T0XICITY</title>
    <link>https://T0XICITY.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on T0XICITY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Patrick Klingenberg</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 21:04:06 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://T0XICITY.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google XSS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/xss-game.appspot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 21:04:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/xss-game.appspot/</guid>
      <description>Google XSS Game In this post I solve the Goolge beginners XSS challanges. These are easier and especially recommended for beginners.
Level 1: Hello, world of XSS This entry-level task is a simple example of XSS. No matter which payload is placed where, it is executed.
Payload: // In the input field &amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; //In the url frame?query=&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; The code is integrated into the application without further verification, so that the browser understands and executes it as part of the page code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google CTF 2019</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/googlectf2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 15:22:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/googlectf2019/</guid>
      <description>Google CTF 2019 Writeup 1. Enter Space-Time Coordinates After Downloading the attachment we can run the file command to get additional information. patrick@VB:~/Desktop/Google1$ file 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed: Zip archive data, at least v2.0 to extract As we can see the file is an Zip archive - So let&amp;rsquo;s just unzip it! patrick@VB:~/Desktop/Google1$ unzip 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed Archive: 00c2a73eec8abb4afb9c3ef3a161b64b451446910535bfc0cc81c2b04aa132ed extracting: log.txt extracting: rand2  We get two files log.txt and rand2. patrick@VB:~/Desktop/Google1$ cat rand2  Running the cat command on the rand2 file shows us the first flag:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development process of this website</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 17:41:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/this-website/</guid>
      <description>How i got the idea to create a static website This website was created during my semester break. originally I had an unused Raspberry Pi 3 that i wanted to use as a webserver for hosting a website using the Wordpress Content-Management-System.
Long story in brief - I installed LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP) on the pi and found that the performance of the website was not exactly what I had in mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our enterprise. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the Patrick Klingenberg. The use of the Internet pages of the Patrick Klingenberg is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from the data subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>## About</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this website is to provide me with a medium in which I can publish my thoughts and work on topics that interest me. On the one hand, this has the purpose of allowing me to recapitulate topics for myself and, in addition, to make them available to other interested parties.
The name T0XICITY is derived from the song Toxicity by the fantastic band System of a Down ♪♫</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>