<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>T0XICITY</title>
    <link>https://T0XICITY.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on T0XICITY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Patrick Klingenberg</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 11:57:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://T0XICITY.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuckoo Sandbox Installation Guide</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/cuckoo_sandbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 11:57:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/cuckoo_sandbox/</guid>
      <description>Cuckoo Sandbox The Cuckoo Sandbox is an open source software for automatic analysis of suspicious files. It uses custom components that monitor the behavior of malicious processes while they are running in an isolated environment.
This manual describes the installation of the Cuckoo Sandbox and its modules. Since setting up the sanbdox can sometimes cause a lot of difficulties I have found some useful workarounds for my issues, which I would like to publish here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google XSS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/xss-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 21:04:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/xss-game/</guid>
      <description>Google XSS Game In this post I solve the Goolge beginners XSS challanges. These are easier and especially recommended for beginners.
Level 1: Hello, world of XSS This entry-level task is a simple example of XSS. No matter which payload is placed where, it is executed.
Payload: // In the input field &amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; //In the url frame?query=&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(0)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; The code is integrated into the application without further verification, so that the browser understands and executes it as part of the page code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital warfare in Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/digital_warfare_ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 18:55:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/blog/digital_warfare_ukraine/</guid>
      <description>Digital warfare in Ukraine This report deals with digital warfare at the example of cyber activities conducted in the Ukrainian conflict. It shows how digital warfare has evolved over time and how Ukraine has become a testing ground for cyberweapons. It discusses the difficulties of assigning and preventing cyber-attacks. Based on a ransomware attack in 2017 this report will show that cyber warfare is much more than a theoretical threat. It will highlight the impact of the malware attack NotPetya, as well as the reaction of politics and computer experts to the occurred events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our enterprise. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the Patrick Klingenberg. The use of the Internet pages of the Patrick Klingenberg is possible without any indication of personal data; however, if a data subject wants to use special enterprise services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary. If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from the data subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://T0XICITY.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Patrick Klingenberg, I am 25 years old and a computer science student 🎓
The purpose of this website is to provide me with a medium in which I can publish my thoughts and work on topics I am interested in. On the one hand, this has the purpose of allowing me to recapitulate topics for myself and, in addition, to make them available to other interested folks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>